<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2021 on Winja</title>
    <link>https://www.winja.site/tags/2021/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2021 on Winja</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 16:05:31 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.winja.site/tags/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Winja CTF | C0C0N 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.winja.site/past-events/winja-ctf-12nov2021-c0c0n/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 16:05:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.winja.site/past-events/winja-ctf-12nov2021-c0c0n/</guid>
      <description>Winja organised Capture-the-Flag competition for all, women and men participants, at c0c0n 2021 security and hacking virtual conference.
 Event Details   Official CTF Writeups  By Sneha Surana (D@e77$ep, b74ass, Esoteric, Hardy) By Sanjay Das (Cha-Cha-Cha, MyProfile, 1NoCLI, MissConfig, Andromeda) By Aravindha Hariharan (Reciprical Cipher, BlogQL, Circle Cipher, The Valet, Hash Map, Believe Your Eyes)   Community Writeups  Believe Your Eyes, Find My Address, Hardy, Reciprical Cypher, Decode Me, D@e77$ep, BlogQL, The Valet - By NilbinSec Esoteric, Believe Your Eyes, Hardy, Anonymous, b74ass - By aman333nolawz Cha-Cha-Cha - By MustafaRaad7 Bomb Defusal - By MustafaRaad7 D@e77$ep - By fl4M3x BlogQL - By sinnerx9 Anonymous - By exploit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winja Talks | 09 September 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.winja.site/past-events/winja-talks-09sep2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.winja.site/past-events/winja-talks-09sep2021/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;So you want to get into Cybersecurity?&amp;rdquo; by Aditi Bhatnagar. This talk was focused on speaker&amp;rsquo;s journey into the field of cybersecurity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winja Talks | 26 August 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.winja.site/past-events/winja-talks-26aug2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.winja.site/past-events/winja-talks-26aug2021/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Building Resilient Communities&amp;rdquo; by Shivani Singh. This talk was focused on creating communities that are robust, resilient, diverse and what goes behind building something like this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>